<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cisco Intersight Help Center – Data Type</title>
    <link>http://localhost:8080/tags/data-type/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Type on Cisco Intersight Help Center</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:23:12 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="http://localhost:8080/tags/data-type/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Data Type</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/docs/ico/datatype/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 15:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/docs/ico/datatype/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Data types also specify boundaries for values, and constraints like regular expressions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cisco Intersight provides a whole range of system-defined data types
that you can use in your workflows. In addition, you can also create a
data type in Cisco Intersight. To view all data types that are currently
available or configured, choose Orchestration &lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Data Types. A
dashboard displays the following details under these tabs, namely, My
Data Types, System Data Types, and All Data Types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Number of Composite Type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Number of System Defined Data Type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can view a tabular list of data types with the following
information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference Name&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display Name&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Composite Type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last Updated&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this screen, as an Account Administrator, or as a user with
Workflow Designer privileges, you can perform the following actions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create a new data type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edit or delete a custom data type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clone a data type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; You cannot edit or delete a system-defined data type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many input types defined in Cisco Intersight representing a
broad selection of categorical, numeric, and text parameters. For
example, some existing data types are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generic Text Input (the least restricted input type)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IPv4 Address&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OS Type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Memory Size Selector&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Primitive data type&amp;mdash;Represents primitive data like String, Float,
Integer, Boolean, Json, or Enum. Following are the attributes
specific to primitive data types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Secure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Constraints (specifies limits and boundaries for values)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Object Selector (lists the Cisco Intersight managed object
selectors). This attribute is available only when the primitive
data is String. Following are the attributes specific to Object
Selector:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intersight API Reference&amp;mdash;Enter the URL of the Intersight
API configured with parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Selector Attribute&amp;mdash;Enter the attribute name(s) that needs
to be displayed in the input table column. You can add
multiple selector attributes by clicking +.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Value Attribute&amp;mdash;Enter the value to be passed as an input
while executing a task. This value should be any one of the
attribute name specified in the Selector Attribute field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Array data type&amp;mdash;Represents an array of a given type. It can be an
array of primitive data, reference data, or of custom data type.
Following are the attributes specific to array data types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ArrayItemType&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Min&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MoReference data type&amp;mdash;Represents Cisco Intersight Managed object
reference. Following are the attributes specific to reference data
types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intersight API Reference&amp;mdash;Enter the URL of the Intersight API
configured with parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Selector Attribute&amp;mdash;Enter the attribute name(s) that needs to
be displayed in the input table column. You can add multiple
selector attributes by clicking +.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Target data type&amp;mdash;Represents a target endpoint or device. Following
are the attributes specific to target data types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intersight API Reference&amp;mdash;Enter the URL of the Intersight API
configured with parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Selector Attribute&amp;mdash;Enter the attribute name(s) that needs to
be displayed in the input table column. You can add multiple
selector attributes by clicking +.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Support Objects&amp;mdash;Enter the object filter used for mentioning
the interesting object in the task definition. You can add
multiple support objects by clicking +.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Constraint Attribute&amp;mdash;Enter the attribute used for defining
decision conditions to choose the right implementation task. You
can add multiple constraint attributes by clicking +.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Connector Attribute&amp;mdash;Enter the attribute used for defining what
value to be passed as input to the implementation task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Custom data type&amp;mdash;Allows defining type constraints once and then
use them in multiple tasks and workflows. Following are the
attributes specific to target data types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Custom Data Type Name&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Catalog Moid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You choose existing input types from a list that displays a name, type,
and category for each variable. The list can be filtered to make finding
a given data type manageable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If none of the existing data types serves your need in a particular
application, it is possible to create custom data types by defining
restrictions on existing data types.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;creating-a-data-type&#34;&gt;Creating a Data Type&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To create a data type, perform the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose Orchestration from the left navigation pane and click Data
Types.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose Create Data Type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Create Data Type screen, enter the following information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organization&amp;mdash;Choose an organization from the drop-down list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Name&amp;mdash;Enter a name for the custom data type definition. The name
can be alphanumeric and can include a combination of upper case and
lower case letters and special characters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Label&amp;mdash;Enter a label that helps you identify the data type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description&amp;mdash;Enter a description, if required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set Tags&amp;mdash;Enter a tag in the key:value format, if required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select the parameters for the data type&amp;mdash;Choose Simple or
Composite. A Simple data type has only a singular value, while a
composite data type has multiple properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;20&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For example, a LoginName is a simple data type whereas a
MailingAddress would be a Composite data type (with street, city,
state, and so on.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Target data type is not supported when you choose Composite
as a parameter input.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To add additional inputs, click Add Field and click New Definition.
Then, enter the following information:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Name&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Label&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Required&amp;mdash;Update this field only when you are adding a Composite
data type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Type&amp;mdash;Choose a data type for primitive data type. For example,
String, Integer, Float, Boolean, Json, Enum, MoReference, Target
Data Type, or custom data type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The fields displayed depend on the value you select for the Type
field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you select the data type as Enum, specify the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  Enum List&amp;mdash;Enum label and value. You can add multiple selector
attributes by clicking +.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  Widget type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you select the data type as String, specify the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  Minimum and MaximumRange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  Regex&amp;mdash;Validates the regular expression when you select String
in the Type field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c.  Secure&amp;mdash;Indicates that the values of these properties are
encrypted and stored in Cisco Intersight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;d.  ObjectSelector&amp;mdash;Enable to configure the Intersight managed
object selectors. This attribute is available only when the
primitive data is String. Specify the Intersight API Reference
and selector attributes to feed the input from the table
selection. Value will be passed according to the configuration
set in the Value attribute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you select the data type as Integer or Float, specify the
following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  Minimum and MaximumRange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you select the data type as MoReference, specify the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  Intersight API Reference&amp;mdash;Enter the URL of the Intersight API
configured with parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  Selector Attribute&amp;mdash;Enter the attribute name(s) that needs to
be displayed in the input table column. You can add multiple
selector attributes by clicking +.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you selected a composite data type, you can specify the field
mapping details. With field mapping, you can pass the value from the
parent composite data type to a child composite data type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;21&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To specify the field mapping, do the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  Key&amp;mdash;The input field that you want to hide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  Value Attribute&amp;mdash;The value in a template style to be passed
dynamically during the execution. The inputs are referenced as
\${datatype.type.AttributeName}.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;11&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click Add.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To add a Parameter Set rule, click Add Rule &amp;gt; Parameter Set.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;22&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information, see &lt;strong&gt;Error! Reference source not found.&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  Name&amp;mdash;The name of the Parameter Set rule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  If Field&amp;mdash;Select the input field that will be used for the
Parameter Set rule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c.  Condition&amp;mdash;The condition for the rule. The condition can be
Equal to, Not equal to, Contains, or Matches Pattern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;d.  Value&amp;mdash;The value of the input (If Field) that will be used for
the Parameter Set rule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;e.  Field to be shown&amp;mdash;Select input fields that should be made
available when the Parameter Set rule condition is satisfied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;f.  Click Save.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;13&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click Preview to validate the definitions that you have added and
make corrections, if required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click Add.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;23&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The data type that you added is displayed in the tabular list on the
Data Types screen. You can now create a workflow and use this data
type in the workflow input. Similar to workflows, you can define the
Parameter Set rules at custom data type level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-type-parameter-set-rule&#34;&gt;Data Type Parameter Set Rule&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you create a composite data type, you can specify the fields for
the data type. After you define the fields, you can set a Parameter Set
rules. The Parameter Set rule control the availability of specific
parameters or inputs during the execution. After the first input is
specified, the Parameter Set rule controls which subsequent input fields
are made available during the execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; You can define a Parameter Set rule only for a custom data
type that has more than two input fields with the supported data type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The supported data types for the Parameter Set rules are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boolean&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enum&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;String Object Selector&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MoReference&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example: The following example shows how to create a Parameter Set rule
for a composite data type with four fields. The composite data type
fields are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cluster Type&amp;mdash;Type is &lt;em&gt;Enum&lt;/em&gt; and Enum list is &lt;em&gt;VM&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;HX&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VMware Cluster&amp;mdash;Type is &lt;em&gt;String&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HX Cluster&amp;mdash;Type is &lt;em&gt;String&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cluster Description&amp;mdash;Type is &lt;em&gt;String&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can create two Parameter Set rules. During the execution when the
Cluster Type value is &lt;em&gt;VM&lt;/em&gt; only VMware Cluster field is made available.
Alternately, when the Cluster Type value is &lt;em&gt;HX&lt;/em&gt;, only HX Cluster is
made available. The details of the Parameter Set rules are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rule1&amp;mdash;If Field is &lt;em&gt;Cluster Type&lt;/em&gt;, Condition is &lt;em&gt;Equal to&lt;/em&gt;, Value
is &lt;em&gt;VM&lt;/em&gt;, and Fields to be shown is &lt;em&gt;VMware Cluster.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rule2&amp;mdash;If Field is &lt;em&gt;Cluster Type&lt;/em&gt;, Condition is &lt;em&gt;Equal to&lt;/em&gt;, Value
is &lt;em&gt;HX&lt;/em&gt;, and Fields to be shown is &lt;em&gt;HC Cluster.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cloning-a-data-type&#34;&gt;Cloning a Data Type&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can clone a data type. The cloned data type is identical to the
original data type. You can edit the new data type immediately. You
might do this, for example, to create a data type that is similar to the
source data type that can be edited based on your requirements. The new
data type has a new, separate version history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To clone a data type, complete the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose Orchestration from the left navigation pane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click Data Type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the tabular list of data types, select a data type and choose
Clone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Clone Data Type screen, edit the user-friendly short name,
reference name, description, and organization details. The
organization mappings are displayed only for pre-canned data types
and not for the custom data types.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check the Open Clone in Editor check box if you want to open the
cloned data type and edit the details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click Clone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;exporting-a-data-type&#34;&gt;Exporting a Data Type&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intersight Cloud Orchestrator enables you to export data types from an
account to your system and then import them to another account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To export a data type, complete the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose Orchestration from the left navigation pane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click Data Type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the tabular list of data types, do one of the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select a data type, click the Ellipsis (&amp;hellip;) icon in the same row,
and then choose Export Data Type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select multiple data types, click the Ellipsis (&amp;hellip;) icon from the
header or footer of the tabular list, and then choose Export Data
Type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Export Data Type screen:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  In the JSON File Name field, use the default filename or enter a
filename of your choice for the JSON file that stores the data
type components.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  Use the Export Tags toggle button to include or exclude the
user-defined tags. ICO does not export the system-defined tags.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c.  Click Export.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;d.  Save a local copy of the JSON file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;importing-a-data-type&#34;&gt;Importing a Data Type&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intersight Cloud Orchestrator enables you to import data types to your
account by importing a JSON file that contains the data type components.
You can create the JSON file by exporting the data type components from
another account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To import a data type, complete the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose Orchestration from the left navigation pane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click Data Type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click Import.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;24&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Import wizard appears.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Select File screen:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  From the Organization drop-down list, choose the organization to
which you want to import the data type(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  Click Browse, and then select the JSON file that contains the
data type(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensure that the file size of the JSON file is not more than
1MB. If the file size is more than 1MB, export the data type(s) in
batches, and then try import.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c.  Click Next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;25&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intersight Cloud Orchestrator validates the JSON file and displays
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the data type(s) in the Details screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Details screen:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  To associate an additional tag to the components listed in the
table, enter the tag in the Set Tags field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Set Tags is an optional field. You must enter the tag in the
key:value format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  If one or more data type components are already available in the
system, choose a rule to replace or skip the duplicate components.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c.  Click Import.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Import Result screen:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  Verify the status of the imported data type(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b.  If you want to view the details of the import request:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click the link displayed above the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, click the Requests icon displayed in the menu bar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;!-- --&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information, see
&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:8080/docs/ico/wokflowdesigner/#requests&#34;&gt;Requests&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a.  Click Close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Template Syntax (Go Template)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/docs/ico/cheatsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:23:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/docs/ico/cheatsheet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;referencing-variables-in-the-workflow-designer&#34;&gt;Referencing variables in the Workflow Designer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Usage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Code&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Workflow Input&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;You can reference a workflow input by replacing NAME with the the reference name you have given it inside the workflow designer&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{.global.workflow.input.NAME}} &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Task Output&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;You can reference a task output by replacing TASK with the name of the task (from the Code view), and by replacing NAME with the name of the output&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{.global.TASK.output.NAME}}   &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Org Moid&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Moid of the Intersight org used to execute this workflow&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{.security.OrganizationMoid}}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;referencing-variables-in-the-task-designer&#34;&gt;Referencing variables in the Task Designer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Usage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Code&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Task Input&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;You can reference a task input by replacing NAME with the the reference name you have given it inside the task designer&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{.global.task.input.NAME}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sub-Task Output&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;You can reference a sub-task output by replacing SUBTASK with the reference name of the sub-task, and by replacing NAME with the name of the output&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{.global.SUBTASK.output.NAME}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;advanced-functions&#34;&gt;Advanced functions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Usage&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Code&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Conditional&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Will allow you to select what option you want to execute based on a conditional. Replace VALUE with the specific value you want to compare against.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{if (eq .global.workflow.input.example VALUE)}}IF TRUE{{else if eq .global.workflow.input.example VALUE}}ELIF TRUE{{else}}ELSE{{end}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Optional variable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Only executes a block of the template if the variable was provided in the input. Inside of the with block, you refer to the name of the original variable as $x (or whatever variable you use)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{with $x := .global.workflow.input.example}}{{$x}}{{end}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Regex&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Apply a regex pattern to a string to filter out a sub-string. Replace REGEX with your regex pattern. This can be combined with the index feature below to filter out the n-th sub-string.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{FindAllString .global.workflow.input.example &amp;ldquo;REGEX&amp;rdquo;}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Get n-th entry&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Allows you to get the n-th entry from a list. Replace NUMBER with the position of the list item you want to select.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{index .global.workflow.input.example NUMBER}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sub-parameter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Allows you to select the subparameter of a previous operation. Replace SUBELEMENT with the parameter you are looking for&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{(index .global.workflow.input.example NUMBER).SUBELEMENT}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Loop&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Allows you to loop through a list and execute a template for each entry in the list. If you want to prepend something to your list, you can use if $index to only apply on the first pass of the loop&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{range $index, $element := .global.workflow.input.example}}{{$element}}{{end}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;List length&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Get the length of a list&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;{{len .global.workflow.input.example}}&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
